Guide to the Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations records, 1990 UA 112
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations records
1990
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 112
14 Linear Feet 24 boxes
Event planning documents, correspondence, notes, drafts, memos, press releases, newsclippings, photographs and memorabilia created and maintained by Rice University in support of the 1990 Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations, hosted by Rice University.
Biographical / Historical
Perhaps no other event so represented Rice's emerging role as a national, even international, institution, than its being chosen to host the 1990 Economic Summit of the Industrialized Nations. For three days in July heads of delegations from the United States, Great Britain, Germany, France, Italy, Japan, Canada, and the European Economic Community held talks at Rice, covered by thousands of journalists and communicated to the world. Rice had long hosted major world figures—General Pershing; Presidents (or presidents-to-be) Taft, Hoover, Eisenhower, Kennedy (announcing the goal of going to the moon), Johnson, Carter, Reagan; Sir Harold Wilson; Prince Philip; and the Dalai Lama suggest the range of famous visitors. But never had such an assemblage appeared at one time as during the Economic Summit. Alumni around the globe were thrilled to see on television world political leaders walking through the familiar arches of Lovett Hall.
Excerpted from Dr. John Boles' "A University So Conceived: A Brief History of Rice" (Revised Edition), 1997, p. 81.
Scope and Contents
Event planning documents, correspondence, notes, drafts, memos, press releases, newsclippings, photographs and memorabilia created and maintained by Rice University in support of the 1990 Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations, hosted by Rice University.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Boxes 1-16 and 18-24 stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Box 17 stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Acquisition Information
These records were transferred from the University Relations Department, the Albert Thomas Convention Center, Rice Summit Office, Office of University Relations, Office of News and Publications, Tommy LaVergne (photographs), Coordinator of Foreign Language Volunteers, Rice University President's Office; 1990-1996.
Index Terms
Subjects
Politics and government; Houston Economic Summit; Universities and colleges
Document Types
clippings (information artifacts); notes; memorabilia; corrrespondence; press releases; photographs
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University.
- Series I: General, 244699
  - AAA Complementary Summit Map, 244802 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Apple Computer, February – July 1990, 244801 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Apple Computer, Rice University Information from Hypercard Stack, 244800 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Attractions Association, Houston, 244799 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baker & Botts, 244798 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Broccoli, 244797 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 244796 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Calendar of Events, 244795 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cannata Communications (Video), 244794 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Center for Education at Rice University, 244793 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 244792 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Continuing Studies, 244791 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Credentialing, 244790 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Damages, 244789 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Donations, 244788 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Facilities, May 1989 – January 1990, 244787 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Facilities, February – March 1990, 244786 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Facilities, April – May 1990, 244785 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Facilities, June – August 1990, 244784 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Final Communique, 244783 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fleishman – Hillard (Public Relations) January – February 1990, 244782 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fleishman – Hillard (Public Relations) March 1990, 244781 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fleishman – Hillard (Public Relations) April – July 1990, 244780 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Food, 244779 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Founder's Room Information, 244778 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Great Meetings," Steve Barnhill & Company, 244777 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Henderson NASA Exhibit, 244776 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Houston Grand Opera, 244775 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Houston: Image and Imagination," Valentin Gertsman, 244774 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Houston Summit Committee, September – November 1990, 244773 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Houston Summit Committee, December – May 1990, 244772 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Houston Summit Committee, June – July 1990, 244771 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Invitations and Tickets, 244770 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Japanese Business Media (Tour), 244769 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Kids' Summit (HISD), 244768 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Killgore Productions ("Great Meetings" Video), 244767 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Kohn – Cruikshank, January – March 1990, 244766 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Kohn – Cruikshank, April – June 1990, 244765 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Kohn – Cruikshank, Rice Interview Notes, 244764 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kohn – Cruikshank, "Rice University: Setting the Standard", 244763 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Latin Translations, 244762 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Letters from Leanne Woodward's Third-Grade Class, West University Elementary School, 244761 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Media and Public Relations Plan for Rice University, 244760 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Media Committee, 244759 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Media Planning (Material from Binder), 244758 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Media Training, 244757 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Moves, 244756 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 244755 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "On Campus" (Newsletter), 244754 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Parking Tags, 244753 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Personnel, 244752 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Planning Design Research (PDR), 244751 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations Search, 244750 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "R" Room, 244749 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rice Economic Summit Status Report, 244748 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rice Institute for Policy Analysis (RIPA) Symposium, 244747 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rice Summit Project Task Force, 244746 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rice Summit Proposal (Original), 244745 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rice Summit Proposal (Revised), 244744 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Rice University Guidebook for the 1990 Economic Summit of Industrial Nations", 244743 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Rice University Information", 244742 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secret Service (United States), 244741 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Secret Words Puzzle, 244740 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Security (Rice University), 244739 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sights of Houston Subcommittee, 244738 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Site Visit (December 14, 1989), 244737 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Site Visit Notebook (November 17, 1989), 244736 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Site Visit Notebook (January 9, 1990), 244735 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Site Visit Notebook (February 1990), 244734 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Site Visits, 244733 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Southgate Civic Club, 244732 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - South Main Center Association, 244731 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Southwestern Bell, 244730 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stationery, 244729 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Summit Archive Project, 244728 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Summit Commemorative, Constellation of Nations, 244727 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Summit Gala, 244726 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Summit Preparedness, 244725 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Summit Press Material, 244724 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Summit Schedule, 244723 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Summit Talk", 244722 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Summit Tour Invitation Letters, 244721 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Temporary Reassignment of Employees, 244720 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Temporary Telephone Directories, 244719 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Texas Monthly" magazine, 244718 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Thank You Letters (Non-Rice), 244717 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Thank You Letters (Rice), 244716 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Thank You Letters to George Rupp, 244715 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Thank You Letters to George Rupp, (VIP), 244714 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Thank You Party, 244713 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Thresher Project, 244712 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Tiffany Etched Glass Pieces, 244711 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Timelines, 244710 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - United Exposition Service Company, 244709 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - University Relations, 244708 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "A View from the Summit" by George Rupp, 244707 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - VIP Reception, 244706 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers, 244705 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Washington Summit Office, November 1989 – March 1990, 244704 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Washington Summit Office, April 1990, 244703 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Washington Summit Office, May 1990 – August 1990, 244702 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Weekly Advisory Memos, 244701 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Williamsburg Visit, December 1989, 244700 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series II: Media, 244644
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,, November – December 1989, 244698 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,, September – December 1989, 244697 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,, January – March 1990, 244696 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,, January – March 1990, 244695 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,April 1990, 244694 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,May 1990, 244693 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Copies from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle,May 1990, 244692 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Houston Press Clippings, June 1990, 244691 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, June 1 – 21, 1990, 244690 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, June 2 – 8, 1990, 244689 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, June 22 – 30, 1990, 244688 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, June 24 – 30, 1990, 244687 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 1 – 6, 1990, 244686 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Chronicle, July 1-2, 1990, 244685 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 4 – 6, 1990, 244684 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 7 – 8, 1990, 244683 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 9, 1990, 244682 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 10 – 11, 1990, 244681 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 10 – 11, 1990, 244680 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 12 – 15, 1990, 244679 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 16, 1990 – June 21, 1991, 244678 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings from The Houston Post and The Houston Chronicle, July 16 – October 10, 1990, 244677 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings from various publications, 244676 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Copies from various publications, 244675 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings from The Rice Thresher, 244674 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings from The Rice Reader, 244673 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, Texas, November 1989 – January 1990, 244672 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, United States, February – June 1990, 244671 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rice News Notes (University Relations) June 1990, 244670 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 1 – 7, 1990, 244669 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 8, 1990, 244668 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rice News Notes (University Relations) July 1 – 8, 1990, 244667 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 9, 1990, 244666 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 10, 1990, 244665 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Wire Reports, July 10, 1990, 244664 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 11, 1990, 244663 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rice News Notes (University Relations) July 9 – 11, 1990, 244662 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Rice News Notes (University Relations) July 9 – 11, 1990, 244661 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 12, 1990, 244660 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 13 – 15, 1990, 244659 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, United States, July 16 – 31, 1990, 244658 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Rice News Notes (University Relations) July 12 – 31, 1990, 244657 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, United States, August – December 1990, 244656 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, Canada, 244655 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, China, 244654 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, France, 244653 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, Germany, 244652 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, Hungary, 244651 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, Italy, 244650 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, Japan, 244649 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, Malaysia, 244648 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, South Africa, 244647 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, Switzerland, 244646 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, United Kingdom, 244645 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Series III: Photographs, 244619
  General note
  See also Series V: Memorabilia for additional photographs.
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Heads of Government, O'Connor Reading Room, Day 2, Herring Hall", 244643 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Geoffrey Winningham and Thomas LaVergne, Snapshots at George R. Brown Convention Center, 244642 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Geoffrey Winningham and Thomas LaVergne, Snapshots at Rice University, 244641 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Heads of Delegation at Herring Hall, Day 2", 244640 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Plenary Session in Founder's Room, Heads of Delegation", 244639 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Pre-Summit Rodeo and Western Cookout at Astroarena", 244638 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "'Class Photo,' Academic Quadrangle, Day 1", 244637 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Day 1 Greeting", 244636 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Walking Photo Opportunity, Day 2", 244635 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Herring Hall Offices", 244634 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Geoffrey Winningham, "Dinner at the Museum of Fine Arts Houston, Evening, Day 2", 244633 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - "Preparation", 244632 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Pre-Summit Clean-up", 244631 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Platform Preparation", 244630 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Brochstein's Table", 244629 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Grounds Preparation", 244628 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Tree Planting", 244627 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Cohen House Patio", 244626 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "George R. Brown Convention Center", 244625 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Color Guard and Band", 244624 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Power Preparation", 244623 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Protest Groups and Police", 244622 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Thomas LaVergne, "Thank-You Party at University of Houston, Downtown", 244621 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Uncredited Photos, 244620 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Series IV: Press Releases, 244600
  - Canada, 244618 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Human Rights Foundation, 244617 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Envirosummit, 244616 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - European Community (Material in English), 244615 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - European Community (Material in Japanese), 244614 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - France, 244613 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - George R. Brown Convention Center, 244612 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Germany, Federal Republic of, 244611 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Houston Parks and Recreation, 244610 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Japan, 244609 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NASA, 244608 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pool Reports, 244607 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sierra Club, 244606 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Summit Press Office, 244605 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Texans United, 244604 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Texas, Office of the Governor, 244603 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - United States Information Agency, 244602 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - White House Press Releases, July 9, 1990, 244601 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Series V: Memorabilia, 244556
  - Jean McCaine (Volunteer) Memorabilia, 244599 (Box 16)
  - Jean McCaine Tiffany commemorative bookmark, 244598 (Box 16)
  - "Sallyport" 47.1 (Fall 1990), 244597 (Box 16)
  - Cassette tapes of Jeff Cruikshank interviews: George Rupp, February 22, 1990; Allen Matusow, February 23, 1990; William Martin, February 23, 1990; Kenneth Kennedy, March 1, 1990, 244596 (Box 16)
  - "The Houston Post," Special Education Section, May 17, 1990, 244595 (Box 16)
  - "The Houston Chronicle," Special Section, July 8, 1990, 244594 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Uncredited, 16"x20"): "'Light Sticks' in Front of George R. Brown Convention Center"; "Set Up at Miss Ima's (MFA Houston)"; "Herring Hall"; "Ambassador Presenting Prime Minister Kaifu to President Bush"; "Final Work on Air-Conditioned Platform"; "Margaret Thatcher at Bayou Bend"; "'Class Photo' at Bayou Bend", 244593 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Geoffrey Winningham, 16"x20") "Sherpa"; "Heads of Government Walk to Opening Ceremonies", 244592 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Geoffrey Winningham, 16"x20") "Sherpa"; "Heads of Government Walk to Opening Ceremonies", 244591 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Thomas LaVergne, 11"x14"): "The Summit Flag Committee Views Several Sizes of Flags Hanging from Lovett Hall"; "Employee of Commercial Restoration in the Cloisters"; "Pouring Concrete at the Cohen House"; "Replacing a Tree in the Quadrangle"; "Eusebio Franco"; "Brochstein's"; "Summit Table Assembled"; "Moving Vans"; "Rupp, Martin, and Currie at Computer"; "Suzuki Violinists"; "Marti Vest and the Secret Service, Ley Student Center", 244590 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (James Yao, 11"x14"): "Thresher Project Students, Lovett Hall"; "Lovett Hall, Evening Day 3", 244589 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Uncredited, 11"x14"): "Class Photo", "Flags", 244588 (Box 16)
  - Snapshots (Uncredited): "Credentialing"; "Cohen House"; "Various Rice Exteriors"; "George R. Brown Convention Center"; "Herring Hall"; "Fondren Library"; "Lovett Hall and Founders Room"; "Facilities and Engineering"; "Miss Woodward's Third Grade Class", 244587 (Box 16)
  - "Media Handbook" (2 Copies), 244586 (Box 16)
  - "Programme de la Presse", 244585 (Box 16)
  - "The Trip of President and Mrs. Bush to the Economic Summit, Part II", 244584 (Box 16)
  - "Houston's Hot" Fans (4), 244583 (Box 17)
  - Houston Summit Greeting Cards (2), 244582 (Box 17)
  - Texas Medical Center Pride medallion, 244581 (Box 17)
  - "Texas Music Salute to the 1990 Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations— Houston" (cassette tape), 244580 (Box 17)
  - Rice Media information sign, 244579 (Box 17)
  - Economic Summit wine (red table wine), 244578 (Box 17)
  - Economic Summit Edition sparkling wine, 244577 (Box 17)
  - Tee shirts: 1990 Economic Summit Rice University (2 Styles); Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations, Houston Host Committee (2 Styles); Rice Student Association Summit tee shirt; Brown & Root; Halliburton, Economic Summit Volunteer t-shirt, 244576 (Box 17)
  - Summit visor, 244575 (Box 17)
  - Summit plastic bag, 244574 (Box 17)
  - Rice University faculty profile compilation (Video), 244573 (Box 17)
  - Subseries A: Pins, 244562 (Box 17)
    - CBS Newsnet, 244572
    - Japan, 244571
    - France, 244570
    - Rice University (2), 244569
    - Southwestern Bell, 244568
    - Germany, 244567
    - Rice Owl, 244566
    - Sierra Club, 244565
    - Houston Information, 244564
    - Media Fest Host, 244563
  - Credentials: George Rupp; Volunteer (with nametag); Press, 244561 (Box 17)
  - Secret Service thank you gift, 244560 (Box 17)
  - Summit Commemorative, "Constellation of Nations" replacement porcelain flags, 244559 (Box 17)
  - Outer perimeter pass #709 (Box 17)
  - Rodeo ticket (Astrodomain) (Box 17)
  - United States brass table i.d. plaque, 244558 (Box 18)
  - Glass commemorative (Gift of Chuck Hagel), 244557 (Box 18)
- Series VI: "Japan Economic Journal", 244554
  - June-July, 1990, 244555 (Box 19-20, Folder -)
- Series VII: Posters, 244550
  - "The Economic Summit, Houston, Texas, July 9-11, 1990", 244553 (Box 21)
  - "Houston: Image and Imagination, Photographs by Valentin Gertsman" (2 Copies), 244552 (Box 21)
  - "Houston: First Word from the Moon", 244551 (Box 21)
- Series VIII: Photographic Slides
  - Candid shots, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Convention Center, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Construction, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Demonstrations/Security, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Entertainment, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Interiors, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Landscaping, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lovett Hall, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Media, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Opening Ceremonies, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Table, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - World Leaders, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Series IX: Host Committee materials
  - Houston Host Committee bags, 1990 (Box 23, Item 1-2)
  - Planning Documents, Rice Host Committee, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Houston Information Packet, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Press materials, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Delegation information, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)